ANDREY PAVLYCHEV

2D/UI ARTIST

ADDRESS: Moscow, Russia PHONE: +7 (927) 640-85-23

E-MAIL: drawn.loves.you@gmail.com

WEB: http:///drawn.pro, https://dribbble.com/drawn

PROFILE

2D and User Interface artist with more than 10 years experience in artwork production for mobile and social network games.

As for my competency, I have strong knowledge of Adobe software, 2D digital drawing skills with use of Photoshop, Illustrator and Animate (Flash). Experienced in all phases of art development, visual and technical, starting from concept up to the final design.

Being a flexible artist, I can work in a team or figure out solutions individually as well. Self-motivated and organized, able to work within established style and tight deadlines. Passionate about iconography and vector graphics.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE ARTIST

Thailand, Vietnam, Russia | January 2015 - Present

Projects include game assets, icons, app design, UI and logo design etc.

SENIOR 2D ARTIST

GAMELOFT CO. LTD | Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | March 2017 — September 2017

Worked on company's game projects with duties including:

- Game concepts
- UI design
- · Icon design
- · Logo design
- · Marketing and promotional materials

UI DESIGNER

KRIVORUKOFF LLP | Samui, Thailand | March 2014 — January 2015

Worked on mobile games being in charge for:

- · UI restyling
- UI/UX elements wireframing, design and implementation (Unity3D NGUI Framework)
- · Animated UI pre-vis
- · Icon design

Projects: Adventure Era, Unannounced project.

2D ARTIST AND ANIMATOR

NEXTERS (FORMER CRAZYBIT LLC) | Moscow, Russia | July 2010 — March 2014

Browser, Social and Mobile game assets development. Duties included:

- · UI design and animation
- · Sprite animations sequences
- · Flash animation
- · Character skeletal animation
- · Wide variety of icons (Item icons, ability icons, UI icons, app icons etc)
- · Logo design
- · Marketing and promotional materials

Projects: Lost Island, Lost Chapters, Island Experiment, Supernova, Hellout, WarDogs, Soldiers of Fortune, S.O.S, Metro City, Sinners, BOOM!

FLASH DESIGNER

MAIL.RU | Moscow, Russia | December 2009 — July 2010

Worked on several game projects in a mixture of roles including:

- UI design/restyling
- · UI animation
- · Icon design
- · In game items design
- Character Animation

Projects: TimeZero, Juggernaut, Legends: Legacy of the Dragons, Urban Fight, Cosmics: Galactic Wars, Troetsarstvie.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

TIMEZERO LLC | Moscow, Russia | September 2007 — December 2009

Worked on a wide range of projects, from browser MMORPGs to amazing casual Flash games under Facebook and Vkontakte. Was in charge for:

- Graphic design
- · UI design
- · Icon design
- · 2D animations for characters and FX
- · Character gear set design
- · In game items design
- · Flash banners
- · Marketing and promotional materials
- · Merchandise products design

Projects: TimeZero, Destiny Online, BUGS, Evil Tale, Crouching Panda Hidden Moose, Funny War, Dragons, Pyramid.

DESIGNER

ERA LLC | Moscow, Russia | October 2006 — August 2007

Transformed company's website to deliver more appealing interface and better user experience. Managed content. Designed packaging and promotional materials.

EDUCATION

Saransk, Russia | 2002 — 2008

Area Studies Specialist, Mordovia State University.

Saransk, Russia | 1996 — 2001

Pictural Art Department, Saransk State Art School #4.

SKILLS

User Interface design, Interaction design, Wireframes, Icon Design, Game items design, Logo Design, UI and Character animation (2D), Flash and GIF banners.

SOFTWARE

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Flash (Animate CC), Sketch app. Some experience with Adobe After Effects, Unity3D and Spine. Basic knowledge of HTML, CSS. JIRA, Redmine, Trello, GitHub. OSX.